{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_17_277JCM",
                "player_12_277JCM",
                "player_13_277JCM",
                "player_6_277JCM",
                "player_1_277JCM"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                17,
                12,
                13,
                6,
                1
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "crouch",
                "crouch"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with dark skin, beige turtleneck, blue pants, brown shoes",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A man with short dark hair, medium skin, wearing a light blue shirt, dark vest, matching pants, and brown shoes",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -2625.691,
                    660.363,
                    113.988,
                    0,
                    167.55909948534207,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2252.754,
                    677.823,
                    113.994,
                    0,
                    159.84857335862586,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2792.485,
                    850.17,
                    120.365,
                    0,
                    92.17083713790782,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2797.246,
                    715.233,
                    113.949,
                    0,
                    -57.20368455303942,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -2294.477,
                    845.507,
                    120.09,
                    0,
                    -58.44223584786637,
                    0
                ]
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_277JCM"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "Flying"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -2445.497,
                    649.346,
                    300,
                    0,
                    122.51938149015777,
                    0
                ]
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -2529.521,
            731.973,
            113.927
        ],
        "sample_radius": 300.0
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        -2477.62,
        192.142,
        98.226,
        0,
        96.02278060030902,
        0
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_vest, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_man_in_blue_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_man_in_blue_vest or the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_plaid_pants_and_light_brown_turtleneck_sweater, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_man_in_blue_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_vest"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_blue_vest or White_Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_vest",
                    "B. White_Drone"
                ],
                "answer": "B. White_Drone"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to White_Drone, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What is the total number of individuals who are positioned in a crouch?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a prone or lying down position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many drones are observed flying in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Considering all the people in the scene, how many of them are identified as male?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Among all the humans, how many are wearing some form of eyewear?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Among the male individuals, how many are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene possess a black skin color?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the blue plaid pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. liedown"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in the blue vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. running",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What is the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. walking",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What is the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What is the state of the White Drone?",
                "options": [
                    "A. on the ground",
                    "B. landed",
                    "C. Flying",
                    "D. crashing"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Flying"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in blue plaid pants and light brown turtleneck sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in blue plaid pants and light brown turtleneck sweater?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue plaid pants and light brown turtleneck sweater relative to the man in blue vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in blue vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue vest relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue plaid pants and light brown turtleneck sweater relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "D. Behind"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue plaid pants and light brown turtleneck sweater relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the front of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front of"
            }
        }
    }
}